const questionsEasy = [{
    "question": "Clam Chowder originated in which country?",
    "answer": ["Australia", "United Kingdom", "USA", "Spain"],
    "final": 2
},
{
    "question": "What fast food restaurant boasts that you can \"Have it your way\"?",
    "answer": ["Hardees", "In and Out", "Burger King", "Mickey D's"],
    "final": 2
},
{
    "question": "How many secret herbs and spices are there in the Colonel's recipe?",
    "answer": ["11", "At least a million", "Infinity", "Zero"],
    "final": 0
},
{
    "question": "What essential nutrient do you get from meat, poultry, eggs, and fish?",
    "answer": ["Brawndo", "Protein", "Peanut Butter", "Gainz"],
    "final": 1
},
{
    "question": "What bean that originated in East Asia is used for miso, oil, and tofu?",
    "answer": ["Lima Bean", "Magic Bean", "Peanut", "Soy Bean"],
    "final": 3
},
{
    "question": "Who is the celebrity Chef that is the host of Hell's Kitchen?",
    "answer": ["Max Robbins", "Gordon Ramsay", "The Swedish Chef", "Emeril Lagasse"],
    "final": 1
},
{
    "question": "What is the main ingredient in an omelette?",
    "answer": ["Egg", "Love", "Sugar", "Egg Shells"],
    "final": 0
},
{
    "question": "Who is the famous mascot for McDonald's?",
    "answer": ["Ronald McDonald", "Wendy Thomas", "Caillou", "Naruto"],
    "final": 0
},
]
const questionsMed = [{
    "question": "What is the most consumed manufactured drink in the world?",
    "answer": ["Tea", "Beer", "Coca-cola", "Pepsi"],
    "final": 0
},
{
    "question": "A macaron is typically made using which nut?",
    "answer": ["Almonds", "Pistachios", "Peanuts", "Cashews"],
    "final": 0
},
{
    "question": "In which country did Tea originate?",
    "answer": ["Japan", "Thailand", "United Kingdom", "China"],
    "final": 3
},
{
    "question": "Where did Mulligatawny soup originate?",
    "answer": ["Malaysia", "India", "Thailand", "China"],
    "final": 1
},
{
    "question": "Which country has the wine making region known as the Barossa Valley?",
    "answer": ["France", "Australia", "Germany", "Italy"],
    "final": 1
},
{
    "question": "What is actually a fruit, not a veggie?",
    "answer": ["Broccoli", "Tomato", "Potato", "Cauliflower"],
    "final": 1
},
{
    "question": "What ingredient makes a Martini \"Dirty\"",
    "answer": ["Finesse", "Olive Brine", "Onion Juice", "Bleu Cheese"],
    "final": 1
},
]
const questionsHard = [{
    "question": "If you were in Australia and eating a 'sinker' what would you be having?",
    "answer": ["Spaghetti", "Pie", "Fries", "Soup"],
    "final": 1
},
{
    "question": "If you were having a cocktail of Guinness and Champagne what would it be called?",
    "answer": ["Red Velvet", "Blue Velvet", "Black Velvet", "Gold Velvet"],
    "final": 2
},
{
    "question": "What fruit is traditionally used in an Eve's Pudding?",
    "answer": ["Pineapples", "Oranges", "Strawberries", "Apples"],
    "final": 3
},
{
    "question": "Which country is the origin of the beef stew known as Daube?",
    "answer": ["Austria", "Sweden", "France", "Germany"],
    "final": 2
},
{
    "question": "What fast food restaurant is credited with introducing the first modern-day drive-thru window?",
    "answer": ["Mickey D's", "Wendy's", "Burger King", "Taco Bell"],
    "final": 1
},
{
    "question": "Which of the following is in the cruciferous vegetable family?",
    "answer": ["Cabbage", "Tomato", "Cucumber", "Potato"],
    "final": 0
},
{
    "question": "What is the common name for Allium sativum?",
    "answer": ["Tomato", "Garlic", "Kale", "Watermelon"],
    "final": 1
},
{
    "question": "Which of the following is not considered a \"Mother Sauce\"?",
    "answer": ["Hollandaise", "Bechamel", "Veloute", "Bearnaise"],
    "final": 3
},
{
    "question": "Where did \"Spam\" originate?",
    "answer": ["Hawaii", "Mars", "Minnesota", "Tennessee"],
    "final": 2
},
]